module.exports = exports = [
  {
    question: 'At 15 inches wide and 8 inches thick, where was the thickest snowflake ever found?', 
    a: 'North Dakota',
    b: 'Alberta Canada',
    c: 'Siberia',
    d: 'Montana',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where were the first Winter Olympics held?', 
    a: 'Oslo Norway',
    b: 'Lake Placid US',
    c: 'St. Moritz Switzerland',
    d: 'Chamonix France',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the coldest tempterature ever recorded on Earth?', 
    a: '-101째F',
    b: '-146째F',
    c: '-123째F',
    d: '-190째F',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'The largest snowman ever built in Bethel, Maine was how tall?', 
    a: '96ft 7in',
    b: '113ft 7in',
    c: '120ft 6in',
    d: '143ft 9in',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following animals canNOT turn white in the winter?', 
    a: 'Arctic Fox',
    b: 'Ferret',
    c: 'Barren-Ground Caribou',
    d: 'Ptarmigan',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'A single snowstorm can drop up to how much snow?', 
    a: '1 million tons',
    b: '5 million tons',
    c: '24 million tons',
    d: '39 million tons',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What insect can freeze solid during the winter, and thaw back to life in the spring?', 
    a: 'Weta',
    b: 'Black widow',
    c: 'Mosquito',
    d: 'Millipede',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'In what month is the Earth closest to the Sun?', 
    a: 'March',
    b: 'July',
    c: 'December',
    d: 'January',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'The most snow recorded in 24 hours in the US was in Silver Lake, CO. How much fell?', 
    a: '76 inches',
    b: '130 inches',
    c: '92 inches',
    d: '63 inches',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'How much of the Earth\'s surface is covered with glacial ice?', 
    a: '8%',
    b: '10%',
    c: '12%',
    d: '14%',
    answer: 'b'
  },
];